ABONGILE WILLIAM

6 swarthout crescent, PLattekloof 2 · 072 115 1831 abongilewilliam@gmail.com · https://abongile-william.web.app/

I am a 21-year-old ICT Multimedia student currently doing my 3rd year at the Cape Peninsula University of Technology. My current objective is to improve my skills and develop my passion as a Front-End Developer by consistently learning and building projects. My drive and dedication for coding has helped me get this far and I look forward to seeing how I can contribute to the fast-paced industry!

EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2016 – DECEMBER 2016

WOOLWORTHS FLEXIBLE EMPLOYEE, WOOLWORTHS

Working in teams to ensure products are placed and displayed in a neat manner.

Keeps products separated, organized and in good rotation.

Monitors product quality frequently, reporting problems to mitigate safety issues.

Providing excellent customer service, answering questions, and handling complaints from clients.

JANUARY 2019 – FEBUARY 2019

DELIVERY DRIVER, IBUYAMBO

Loading, transporting, and delivering items to clients or businesses in a safe, timely manner. Reviewing orders before and after delivery to ensure that orders are complete, the charges are correct, and the customer is satisfied.

EDUCATION

JANUARY 2018

MATRIC, EDGEMEAD HIGH SCHOOL

Distinction in Computer Applications Technology (Computer Literate) Multiple sport trophies and awards in soccer (Team Player) Successfully obtained Matric Certificate

JANUARY 2019

HIGHER CERTIFICATE IN SOUND PRODUCTION, SAE INSTITUTE

Successfully obtained a Higher Certificate in Sound Production Involved a lot of group work and obtained leadership skills

JANUARY 2019 - CURRENT

ICT IN MULTIMEDIA APPLICATIONS, CAPE PENINSULA UNIVERSITY OF

TECHNOLOGY

2nd year average is 72% Great time management skills Good at working in a team

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- Javascript
- UI/UX design
- Bootstrap
- SQLlite
- Python

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Perseverance and motivation
- Ability to work under pressure
- Leadership
- Confidence

ACTIVITIES

While doing my 3rd year at varsity I also do personal projects to continue improving my skills so that I can contribute to this fast-paced industry!